criticalhit.net 2003-12-03

# Privacy Statement for Critical Hit

Critical Hit has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Critical Hit (criticalhit.co.uk). We are committed to protecting your privacy: we will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998) and will not sell, rent or loan third parties use of or access to personal information such as your name or e-mail address. Please read the following page for more details about our privacy policy.

### What personal information may be collected and by what means?

  * **E-mail**  
We will only use any personal information (such as name, address, and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Though we may retain your e-mail for a period of time, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific enquiry or comments.
  * **Forums**  
This site makes free interactive message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Personal information of registered users is not accessible by the public unless the member adds it to his or her User Information or is disclosed by the user themselves in a public post.
  * **Online Ordering**  
When you place an order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and the card's expiry date. This allows us to process and fulfil your order and to notify you of the status of your order. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by e-mailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly. We do not sell or share any of this information with third parties.

In addition, we sometimes collect information to find out how people found the site, which pages they visited, and how long they stayed. This information does not include any personal information about you. Some examples of this type of data collection are:

  * **IP Addresses**  
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
Our  message boards may display IP addresses along with the message poster's name, e-mail address, and message, but this information is only available to administrators and moderators of the forums.
  * **Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information placed on your computer to help personalize your visit to the site. For example, a cookie will allow us to remember certain things about you, such as your login name for our forums. Most major websites use cookies exactly for this purpose. We cannot tell who you are or where you are with cookies. The cookie only tells us that you have visited the site before and may contain certain information that will help us make your visit more enjoyable.  
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some parts of our website will not function properly if you refuse cookies. For example, you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, or using our forums.

Visitors should be aware that when you are on our site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. For example, if you visit a link, you will leave our site. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.

This site contains links to other sites. Critical Hit is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information.

When our order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number), that information is encrypted. While on a secure page, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. Your credit card details are processed online by our credit card processing company, [Worldpay](http://www.worldpay.com/), in 'real time'; transactions are encrypted using 128 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) architecture. Your credit card details cannot be read or tampered with during transmission. WorldPay uses state of the art security tools and techniques, both proprietary and unique, to ensure that you are protected against what is nowadays a virtually non-existent risk.

### Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  * e-mail: webmaster@criticalhit.co.uk
  * Change information by clicking on the User CP icon on our Forums.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  
Andrew (Webmaster)  
Critical Hit  
e-mail: webmaster@criticalhit.co.uk

* * *

Shop online: [Warhammer 40k Store](http://www.criticalhit.co.uk/acatalog/warhammer_40k.html) \- [Warhammer Store](http://www.criticalhit.co.uk/acatalog/warhammer.html) \- [The Lord of the Rings Store](http://www.criticalhit.co.uk/acatalog/lord_of_the_rings.html)
